<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="cme.xsl" type="text/xsl" media="screen"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>CMEs Online Headlines</title>
<description>
Headlines from the Christian Methodist Episcopal Church
</description>
<link>http://www.cmesonline.org/</link>

    <item> 
      <title>2011 FOCUS Retreat - May 26-29 - Atlanta, GA</title> 
      <description> 
We would like to invite you to the 2011 FOCUS Retreat scheduled to be held Thursday, May 26 - Sunday, May 29, 2011 in Atlanta, Georgia as we "Serve the Present Age through Service and Christian Nurture!" Come and be a part of this spiritual breakthrough. We will be offering Spirit-filled and informative workshops, with topics ranging from 'Love and Relationships' to 'Engaging Young Adults in your Local Church.' There will be awesome Praise and Worship, as well as nightly Worship Services led by renowned Preachers of the Gospel. There will also be opportunities to fellowship with other CMEs across our great Zion and participate in a service project destined to bless the community of Atlanta!
    </description> 
      <link>http://feeds.rapidfeeds.com/?iid4ct=5902782</link> 
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://feeds.rapidfeeds.com/?iid4ct=5902782</guid> 
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2011 13:06:00 EDT</pubDate> 
    </item> 

<item>
<title>The 37th CME General Conference</title>
<description>5 new Bishops Elected</description>
<link>http://www.cmesonline.org/college.php</link>
<pubDate>6/30/2010</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>The CME Forum</title>
<description>You've heard about; Here it is - The CME Forum - News items, controversy and discussion from the C.M.E. connection.</description>
<link>http://www.cmesonline.org/forum/</link>
<pubDate>4/16/2011</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Online Bible</title>
<description>Read the Holy Scriptures using the etext of the King James version. (from Project Gutenberg)</description>
<link>http://www.cmesonline.org/scriptures.php</link>
<pubDate>4/16/2011</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Jamaican Annual Conference 2011</title>
<description>St. Elizabeth Parish Jamaica - April 18-22, 2011</description>
<link>http://www.cmesonline.org/events.php</link>
<pubDate>4/16/2011</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>CME's Online Resources &amp; Links</title>
<description>An interesting array of usefuls links.</description>
<link>http://www.cmesonline.org/linklist.php</link>
<pubDate>4/16/2011</pubDate>
</item>

    <item> 
      <title>Statement from Miles College President, Dr. George French, Concerning Chairman Lockett</title> 
      <description> 
We are greatly saddened by the passing of the Chairman of the Miles College Board of Trustees, Chairman Wallace Edward Lockett. He was elected Chairman of the Board of Trustees in October 2010. Chairman Lockett was a man of faith, serving as Bishop of the Fifth Episcopal District of our great Zion.
    </description> 
      <link>http://feeds.rapidfeeds.com/?iid4ct=5905332</link> 
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://feeds.rapidfeeds.com/?iid4ct=5905332</guid> 
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2011 00:05:00 EDT</pubDate> 
    </item> 

    <item> 
      <title>Bishop Cunningham Elected President of CUIC</title> 
      <description> 
Bishop Ronald M. Cunningham, the 53rd Bishop of the Christian Methodist Episcopal Church, was elected president of Churches Uniting In Christ (CUIC) at their meeting held January 18-20, 2011 in Fort Lauderdale, FL.  Although he was retired at the 2010 General Conference, he continues to serve the church in the capacity of the Ecumenical Bishop.
    </description> 
      <link>http://feeds.rapidfeeds.com/?iid4ct=5902774</link> 
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://feeds.rapidfeeds.com/?iid4ct=5902774</guid> 
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2011 13:04:00 EDT</pubDate> 
    </item> 

    <item> 
      <title>Gala 2011 Celebration Honoring Dr. Elnora P. Hamb - March 25, 2011</title> 
      <description> 
The Balm In Gilead will host Gala Celebration 2011, honoring the leadership and legacy of the international missionary presidents of the three historical African American Methodist denominations: Dr. Elnora P. Hamb (CME Church), Dr. Barbara Shaw (AMEZ Church) and Dr. Jamesina Evans (AME Church). The event will be held on Friday, March 25, 2011, 7:00 p.m., at The Ritz-Carlton Tysons Corner, 1700 Tysons Boulevard in McLean, VA. The Gala Celebration will feature legendary gospel artist Richard Smallwood and Vision. 

This message will provide you with information concerning tickets for Gala Celebration 2011  and hotel accommodations. Please join in honoring our own Dr. Elnora P. Hamb at the Gala Celebration 2011! 
    </description> 
      <link>http://feeds.rapidfeeds.com/?iid4ct=5874173</link> 
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://feeds.rapidfeeds.com/?iid4ct=5874173</guid> 
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2011 10:48:00 EDT</pubDate> 
    </item> 

    <item> 
      <title>Important Information Regarding the 17th Quadrennial Assembly of the Women's Missionary Council - June 25-July 2, 2011</title> 
      <description> 
The 17th Quadrennial Assembly of the Women's Missionary Council will be held June 25 - July 2, 2011 at the Renaissance Schaumburg Hotel &amp; Convention Center in Schaumburg, IL.  This message provides important information to prepare you for the Quadrennial Assembly.  
    </description> 
      <link>http://feeds.rapidfeeds.com/?iid4ct=5874167</link> 
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://feeds.rapidfeeds.com/?iid4ct=5874167</guid> 
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2011 11:44:00 EDT</pubDate> 
    </item> 


    <item> 
      <title>Ninth Episcopal District Spring Convocation 2011 Webcast</title> 
      <description> 
The Ninth Episcopal District Spring Convocation 2011 Webcast
    </description> 
      <link>http://feeds.rapidfeeds.com/?iid4ct=5854571</link> 
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://feeds.rapidfeeds.com/?iid4ct=5854571</guid> 
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 23:25:00 EDT</pubDate> 
    </item> 

    <item> 
      <title>Shared Prayers for the CME Church</title> 
      <description> 
Shared your prayers for the CME Church!
    </description> 
      <link>http://feeds.rapidfeeds.com/?iid4ct=5854557</link> 
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://feeds.rapidfeeds.com/?iid4ct=5854557</guid> 
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 23:11:00 EDT</pubDate> 
    </item> 

    <item> 
      <title>Reflections on Black History Month</title> 
      <description> 
Reflections on Black History Month by the Commission on Social Justice and Human Concerns
    </description> 
      <link>http://feeds.rapidfeeds.com/?iid4ct=5854556</link> 
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://feeds.rapidfeeds.com/?iid4ct=5854556</guid> 
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 23:57:00 EDT</pubDate> 
    </item> 


</channel>
</rss>

